<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pos - Point Of Sale</string>
    <string name="they_say_the_early_bird_catches_the_worm_gross_worms_are_hardly_an_incentive_for_humans_to_get_up_early_unless_you_re_heading_out_to_fish_and_hoping_for_some_free_bait_still_waking_up_early_does_have_some_perks_so_what_re_the_benefits_contemplating_setting_your_alarm_for_an_eye_scorchingly_early_hour_here_s_why_it_might_be_worth_it_more_time_for_yourself_if_you_live_with_other_humans_little_ones_or_adults_getting_up_early_could_give_you_some_much_needed_and_desperately_wanted_time_for_yourself_more_time_to_sip_that_coffee_slowly_while_flipping_through_the_paper_or_just_enjoying_the_silence_can_help_prepare_you_to_face_a_hectic_day_feeling_a_little_more_chill_more_time_to_exercise_if_working_out_is_important_to_you_but_you_often_struggle_to_find_the_time_getting_up_early_could_be_the_ticket_getting_your_exercise_in_first_thing_remedies_the_temptation_to_skip_workouts_because_of_job_or_social_commitments_later_in_the_day_or_plain_old_tiredness_and_while_we_re_on_the_subject_of_feeling_tired_here_s_another_perk_of_morning_workouts_exercise_initiates_a_surge_of_those_feel_good_endorphins_that_can_improve_your_mood_lower_stress_and_anxiety_and_increase_energy_levels_you_re_welcome_less_time_in_traffic_getting_up_and_out_of_the_house_early_can_help_you_beat_the_usual_traffic_which_is_pretty_much_a_universal_plus_less_traffic_doesn_t_just_save_you_time_and_money_it_can_also_help_protect_your_health_and_well_being_as_research_has_linked_sitting_in_traffic_to_stresstrusted_source_depression_aggression_and_rage_respiratory_issues">They say the early bird catches the worm. Gross. Worms are hardly an incentive for humans to get up early, unless you’re heading out to fish and hoping for some free bait. Still, waking up early does have some perks. So, what’re the benefits? Contemplating setting your alarm for an eye-scorchingly early hour? Here’s why it might be worth it. More time for yourself If you live with other humans — little ones or adults  — getting up early could give you some much-needed (and desperately wanted)  time for yourself. More time to sip that coffee slowly while flipping through the paper or just enjoying the silence can help prepare you to face a hectic day feeling a little more chill. More time to exercise If working out is important to you, but you often struggle to find the time, getting up early could be the ticket. Getting your exercise in first thing remedies the temptation to skip workouts because of job or social commitments later in the day or plain old tiredness. And while we’re on the subject of feeling tired, here’s another perk of morning workouts: Exercise initiates a surge of those feel-good endorphins that can improve your mood, lower stress and anxiety, and increase energy levels. You’re welcome. Less time in traffic Getting up and out of the house early can help you beat the usual traffic, which is pretty much a universal plus. Less traffic doesn’t just save you time and money. It can also help protect your health and well-being, as research has linked sitting in traffic to: stressTrusted Source depression aggression and rage respiratory issues</string>
</resources>